inhumanity.com 2018-12-22

# Inhumanity - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is of utmost importance to us. This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") applies to Inhumanity.com (the "Website"). This document details information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on the Website. As noted below, please be aware that we may change our Privacy Policy in the future and it is your obligation to review this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

### Adults Only Service

THIS IS AN ADULTS ONLY SERVICE. We will terminate any accounts which we believe are being used by anyone under the age of eighteen (18) years old or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you view the Website; additionally, we reserve the right to report such person to the proper authorities along with all information provided to us by or with respect to such person.

The Website is not intended for persons under 18-years old. You will only access the Website or register if (1) you are at least 18-years old and (2) have reached the age of majority where you live. The Website prohibits all persons who do not meet the age requirements from accessing the Website. Minors must not access the Website or use its services. If you are under 18-years old, you must not submit information to the Website and must leave the Website immediately.

### Disclosures Made as Necessitated by Law or Safety

All information you provide us with is considered confidential. However, this information may be shared with other third parties as necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement and the court system.

### Data Collected

  * Registration is required for uploading videos and content, and accessing a number of other features. The following personal information is requested at the time of registration: username (required), date of birth (required), and email address (required).
  * Any personal information or content that you voluntarily disclose or upload online becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others.
  * When you visit the Website, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser session. The Website uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. If you remove your persistent cookie, some of the site's features may not function properly.
  * When you visit the Website, our servers may record certain information that your web browser sends such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, platform type, domain names and the date and time of your request.
  * If you contact us by email or other form of communication, we may keep a record of that correspondence.

Third-party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies: Some content or applications on the Website are served by third parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use the Website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content. 

### Uses

  * Your Personally identifiable information submitted to the Website is used to provide to the user the website's features and special personalized features.
  * Your chosen username is displayed to other Users alongside the content you upload, including videos, comments, etc. 
  * Any content that you submit to the Website may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by the general public.
  * We do not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent.
  * We may use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of key website changes or for customer service purposes).
  * We analyze aggregated user traffic information to help streamline our marketing and hosting operations and to improve the quality of the Website. 

### Disclosure of Information

If under duty to do so the Website may release data to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce our Terms Of Service and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property or safety of the Website or our subscribers or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations including the police and governmental authorities for the purposes of protection against fraud or any other kind of illegal activity whether or not identified in the Terms of Service.

Should you deliberately upload any illegal material the Website shall forward all available information to all relevant authorities without notice.

We do not share your personally identifiable information (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their commercial or marketing use without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out.

### Links to Other Websites

The Website contains links to other websites. Please be aware that the Website is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other websites. The Website encourages its customers to be aware when they leave the Website to read the privacy statements of any other website that collects personally identifiable information.

### DMCA Takedown Requests

The Website complies with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA). If you reasonably believe that your copyrighted work has been used or posted by a third party without your consent, you may follow the instructions on our DMCA page on how to report it.

###  Changes to Privacy Policy

The Website will post any changes it makes to this policy on this page. You are responsible for frequently visiting the Website and this policy to check for any changes.
